<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI:Anime</title>
      <link>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>Anime, from English animation — &amp;ldquo;animation&amp;rdquo; is a Japanese animation. Unlike cartoons from other countries, intended mainly for children to watch, most of the anime produced is designed for teenage and adult audiences, and largely due to this it is very popular in the world. Anime is characterized by a characteristic manner of drawing characters and backgrounds. It is published in the form of television series, as well as films distributed on video media or intended for film screening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter V: History anime</title>
      <link>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>The history of anime dates back to the 20th century, when Japanese filmmakers began experimenting with animation techniques invented in the West. The oldest known surviving Japanese animation, &amp;ldquo;Katsudo Shashin&amp;rdquo; lasts only 3 seconds. One of the very first anime was the two-minute comedy film Namakura Gatana, shown in 1917, in which a samurai is about to test his new sword, but is defeated by a townsman. Pioneers in the field of Japanese animation were Shimokawa Oten, Junichi Kochi and Seitaro Kitayama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Peculiarities</title>
      <link>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Japanese animation differs from the animation of other countries, first of all, in that it is a developing closed cultural layer, which includes many unique plot and ideological symbols, templates, stereotypes and types. The simplest examples would be genres specific to anime, such as fur, which live according to their own laws, or elements of Japanese culture that are often reflected in anime.
Anime stands out among animation from other countries due to its relevance in Japanese society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III: Anime production</title>
      <link>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Anime is usually created by small animation studios, and its production is financed by larger companies. The creation of television series usually takes a short time, so small mistakes are not taken into account by the animators. When creating full-length animation, there is more serious quality control, but production deadlines are looser. Orders for a specific anime are formed by producers. An anime director is usually responsible for the art direction of the cartoon, his responsibilities also include casting voice actors and creating a director&amp;rsquo;s storyboard that graphically describes key moments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: Anime genres</title>
      <link>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>The division of anime into genres is very blurry. Anime shares:
By target audience (children, boys, girls, men, women); By storytelling style (comedy, drama, thriller, romance, etc.); By setting and technology (mecha, cyberpunk, school history, fantasy, steampunk, etc.); According to the psychology, goals and nature of the relationships of the characters (sentai, spokon, maho-shojo, harem); By the presence and detail of sexual scenes (ecchi, hentai, yaoi, yuri). Typically, the main characters in anime are characters of gender and age that fit the target audience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: Anime formats</title>
      <link>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Ciel585.github.io/en/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Anime, like other video products, is created with a specific distribution method in mind. These methods include showing on television, in cinemas, selling on video media, and distributing via the Internet. The chosen method leaves its mark on the work, since production processes, budgets, and viewing conditions vary significantly. The most popular formats for anime are television series and OVAs, due to the nature of which they can accommodate a much more detailed story and better develop characters than in a film, but this also determines the reluctance of animators to technical experiments and the predominant role of designers when creating anime.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
